{
    "subject": "resource/Bronis\u0142aw_Kaper",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/linguistics/gold/hypernym",
    "object": "resource/Composer",
    "human_readable": "Bronis\u0142aw Kaper is a Composer.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9743873476982117,
            "question": "When was Bronis\u0142aw Kaper active as a composer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9736201763153076,
            "question": "Is Bronis\u0142aw Kaper a musician?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9545168280601501,
            "question": "What are some famous compositions by Bronis\u0142aw Kaper?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9154605865478516,
            "question": "Who are some other notable composers from the same era as Bronis\u0142aw Kaper?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7576700448989868,
            "question": "What profession is Bronis\u0142aw Kaper known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7500802278518677,
            "question": "In what genres of music does Bronis\u0142aw Kaper work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6736270785331726,
            "question": "What is Bronis\u0142aw Kaper's field of expertise?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5496968626976013,
            "question": "What type of creative work does Bronis\u0142aw Kaper produce?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5277478098869324,
            "question": "Where was Bronis\u0142aw Kaper born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3577069342136383,
            "question": "Has Bronis\u0142aw Kaper won any awards for his work?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Bronis\u0142aw Kaper is a Composer.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4501_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where was Bronis\u0142aw Kaper born?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4501_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of creative work does Bronis\u0142aw Kaper produce?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4501_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Bronis\u0142aw Kaper's field of expertise?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4501_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4501_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4501_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4501_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4501_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4501_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4501_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4501_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4501_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4501_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4501_94.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis response indicates that the information in the documents supports the triple, i.e., Bronis\u0142aw Kaper is indeed a composer. The multiple documents across different file paths confirm this assertion by describing him as a Polish film composer who scored films and musical theater in Germany, France, and the USA."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide information that Bronis\u0142aw Kaper was indeed a film composer, supporting the statement that he is a composer."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}